MiiCharacters.com Privacy Policy
================================

MiiCharacters.com takes the privacy of our visitors' personal information very seriously. This privacy policy covers the types of personal information received and collected by MiiCharacters.com and how such information is used.

Information Collection

MiiCharacters.com may collect and store personal information submitted by users. Information may also be collected through your use of the site, including but not limited to which pages you visited or which links you click.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, MiiCharacters.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files may include your internet protocol ( IP ) address, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), pages you've visited, date and time of your page views, and referring pages. This information may be used to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies, Web Beacons, and Session Information

MiiCharacters.com may use cookies to store information such as personal preferences, user-specific information, or other information sent via your browser. This information is used to personalize and enhance your experience on the site. For example, cookies may be used to store login information and grant access to certain members-only areas of the site.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

We do not share any of your personal information with any third party, except if required to by a court order. Third party advertisers may collect information when you click on or view their advertisements, but do not receive any information directly from MiiCharacters.com.

Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks can use technology which displays the advertisements that appear on our site directly to your browser, enabling them to collect information. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you, or measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. (Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).) If you would like more information about these practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

Limitations and Alternatives

MiiCharacters.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third party advertisers or other websites. You can chose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in third party Internet security programs; however, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as many other websites. This could include the inability to login or store your preferences. More detailed information about cookie management with your specific web browser can be found at your browser's website.

Confidentiality and Security

MiiCharacters.com goes to great lengths to secure all personal data from being viewed or used by any third parties or any parties who do not need access to such information. In the event that you feel your personal data or username and password have been compromised, you should [contact us](http://www.miicharacters.com/contact) immediately.

Privacy Policy changes

MiiCharacters.com may change this privacy policy at any time without notification. However, if we feel that users will be directly affected by a change in the privacy policy, we will make our best effort to notify users of the change.

Questions

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.miicharacters.com/contact).
